Guide to the Paul Revere Reynolds Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Uncataloged Correspondence
  - Rhinehart, Luke (George P. Cockcroft) (Box 140)
  - Riblet, Carl, Jr. and William L Raby (Box 140)
  - Richards, Norman V. (Box 141)
  - Richardson, Stewart (Box 141)
  - Richmond, George (Box 141)
  - Richter, Harvena C. and Conrad Richter (Box 141)
  - Richter, Harvena C. and Conrad Richter (Box 240)
  - Riesenberg, Felix, Jr. (Box 141)
  - Riggs, Lawrason (Box 141)
  - Rigsby, Howard "Vichel Howard" (Box 141)
  - Rigsby, Luraine (Box 240)
  - Rindels, Wayne (Box 142)
  - Rittenhouse, Mignon (Box 142)
  - Rittenhouse, Mignon (Box 240)
  - Rivers, Lucille (Box 240)
  - Rivers, Lucille (Box 142)
  - Roark, Garland "George Garland" (Box 142)
  - Roark, Garland "George Garland" (Box 240)
  - Robbins, Charles (Box 241)
  - Robbins, Charles (Box 142)
  - Robbins, Chris (Box 241)
  - Robbins, Lawrence A. (Box 241)
  - Robinson, Conway (Box 241)
  - Robinson, Conway (Box 142)
  - Robinson, Margaret, A. (Box 241)
  - Rogers, Donald I. (Box 241)
  - Rogers, Samuel (Box 241)
  - Rohmer, Sax "Michael Furey" (Arthur Sarsfield Ward) and Rose Elizabeth Knox "Lisabeth Knox" (Box 241)
  - Rohmer, Sax (Box 142)
  - Rohmer, Sax (Box 143)
  - Rohmer, Sax (Box 144)
  - Rollins College Writers' Conference (Box 241)
  - Rome, Carol Cheney (Box 145)
  - Rooke, Daphne (Box 145)
  - Root, Jonathan (Box 241)
  - Roots, John M. (Box 145)
  - Roscoe, Theodore (Box 145)
  - Rose, Ian F. (Box 241)
  - Rowan, Roy (Box 146)
  - Ruesch, Hans (Box 146)
  - Russell, William (Box 146)
  - S - misc. (Box 147)
  - S - misc. (Box 242)
  - St. Dennis, Dean (Box 242)
  - Salas, Floyd (Box 242)
  - Sale, Mary Loos (Box 147)
  - Sale, Richard (Box 147)
  - Sale, Richard (Box 148)
  - Sale, Richard and Mary Loos Sale (Box 242)
  - Salesman, Jenne Groff (Box 242)
  - Sanchez, Thomas (Box 148)
  - Sanders, Leonard (Box 148)
  - Sand, George X. (Box 148)
  - Sand, George X. (Box 242)
  - Sanders, Leonard (Box 243)
  - Sanderson, Ivan T; The Sanderson Foundation/The Society for the Investigation of the Unexplained (Box 243)
  - Sanderson, Ivan T. (Box 149-152)
  - Sandstrom, Gosta (Box 152)
  - Santos, Ben (Box 152)
  - Sayles, John (Box 152)
  - Scheinfeld, Amram (Box 153)
  - Scheinfeld, Amram (Box 243)
  - Schmidt, James Norman and Margaret (Box 243)
  - Schmidt, James Norman and Margaret Fox Schmidt (Box 153)
  - Schultz, Philip (Box 153)
  - Schultz, Philip (Box 243)
  - Schultz, Stanley K. (Box 153)
  - Schwartz, Stephen (Box 243)
  - Scott, Rachel A (Box 244)
  - Scott, Rachel A. (Box 153)
  - Scott, Thurman T. (Box 153)
  - Scott, Ward (Box 154)
  - Scott, William R. "Weldon Hill" (Box 154)
  - Scott, William R. "Weldon Hill" (Box 244)
  - Scribner's Sons, Charles (Box 155)
  - Seeker and Warburg Limited, Martin (Box 155)
  - Sehon, John L. (Box 244)
  - Selye, Hans (Box 155)
  - Selye, Hans (Box 156)
  - Serrin, William (Box 244)
  - Seton, Cynthia Propper (Box 244)
  - Seton, Cynthia Propper (Box 156)
  - Shabazz, Betty/Estate of Malcolm X (Box 156)
  - Shabecoff, Alice and Phil (Box 244)
  - Shacochis, Bob (Box 245)
  - Shain, Merle (Box 245)
  - Shapiro, Deane, Jr. (Box 156)
  - Shapiro, Susan (Box 245)
  - Sharkey, Joe (Box 156)
  - Sharma, Partap (Box 245)
  - Shaw, George Bernard (Box 156)
  - Sheehan, Ed (Box 245)
  - Sheehy, Gail (Box 245)
  - Sheldon, Naomi (Box 156)
  - Sheldrick, Richard (Box 245)
  - Shellabarger, Samuel and Vifvan (Box 245)
  - Shellabarger, Samuel and Vifvan (Georgia Lovegrove Borg Shellabarger "John Esteven","Peter Loring") (Box 157-159)
  - Shelnutt, Eve (Box 245)
  - Shelnutt, Eve (Box 160)
  - Shelton, Isabelle (Box 245)
  - Sherlock, John (Box 160)
  - Shevey, Sandra jane (Box 245)
  - Shirer, William Lawrence (Box 245)
  - Shister, Neil (Box 160)
  - Shiveley, George (Box 245)
  - Short, Wayne (Box 246)
  - Shubin, Seymour (Box 246)
  - Shurkin, Joel and Lydia Dotto (Box 246)
  - Siegel, Joel E. (Box 246)
  - Sikes, Shirley (Box 246)
  - Sikes, Shirley (Box 160)
  - Silano, Elizabeth (Box 246)
  - Siler, Jack (Box 246)
  - Silverman, Barry G. (Box 160)
  - Simon and Schuster, Inc. (Box 160)
  - Siodmak, Curt (Box 160)
  - Simpson, Ben E. (Box 246)
  - Singer, Felix (Box 246)
  - Siodmak, Curt (Box 246)
  - Sirof, Harriet (Box 246)
  - Skoog, Lawrence C. (Box 246)
  - Slate, Sam J. (Box 246)
  - Slater, Leonard (Box 160)
  - Slykhouse, Gloria B, and Ruthe L. Miller (Box 160)
  - Small, Collie (Box 247)
  - Smith, Bert Kruger (Box 247)
  - Smith, Carlton and Richard Pratt (Box 160)
  - Smith, Doris Buchanan (Box 160)
  - Smith, Doris Buchanan (Box 247)
  - Smith, Ella (Box 247)
  - Smith, Ellen Hart "Jane Murray" (Box l6l)
  - Smith, Frederick E. (Box l6l)
  - Smith, Frederick E. (Box 247)
  - Smith, Howard (Box 247)
  - Smith, Marcine Beaubine (Box 161)
  - Smith, Marshall (Box 161)
  - Smith, Mary and Barbara Isenberg (Box 247)
  - Smith, Susan Carlton (Box 247)
  - Smith, Susan Carlton (Box 161)
  - Smith, Thomas Bell (Box 247)
  - Smythe, Pat (Box 247)
  - Snell, David (Box 247)
  - Soderberg, Dale L. (Box 161)
  - Solomon, Shirl (Box 247)
  - Solow, Martin (Box 247)
  - Sootin, Harry (Box 247)
  - Sootin, Harry (Box 161)
  - Sorensen, Paul G. (Box 247)
  - Soukip, James E. (Box 247)
  - South, Berna Deane (Box 247)
  - Span, Paula (Box 248)
  - Spangler, Larry G. (Box 161)
  - Spencer, Elizabeth (Box 248)
  - Spiering, Frank (Box 248)
  - Spinelle, Thomas F. (Box 161)
  - Spence, Lewis (Box 161)
  - Spivak, Talbot (Box 161)
  - Spivak, Talbot (Box 248)
  - Spring, Clara Thorpe (Box 248)
  - Stacton, David Derek "David Derekson," "Carse Boyd," "Bud Clifton," "David West" (Box 248)
  - Stacton, David (Box 161)
  - Stadtfeld, Curtis K (Box 248)
  - Stadtfeld, Curtis K. (Box 163)
  - Staley, Michael (Box 163)
  - Stambler, Irwin (Box 163)
  - Stambler, Irwin (Box 164)
  - Standish, David (Box 248)
  - Stanton, James (Box 248)
  - tanton, Will (Box 248, Folder 165)
  - Stanwood, Brooks (Box 248)
  - Staples, Mary (Box 249)
  - Stapleton, Constance (Box 249)
  - Stead, Christina (Box 249)
  - Steele, James B. and Donald L. Bartlett (Box 249)
  - Steele, Wilbur Daniel (Box 165)
  - Stein, Sol (Box 165)
  - Stein and Day, Publishers (Box 165)
  - Stein, Sol/ Stein and Day Publishers (Box 249)
  - Steiner, Shari (Box 249)
  - Steiner, Shari and Clyde (Box 165)
  - Stephan, John J. (Box 165)
  - Stephan, Leslie (Box 249)
  - Stephen, Beverly (Box 249)
  - Stern, Philip M. (Box 249)
  - Stern, Rhona (Box 249)
  - Steven, Stewart (Box 249)
  - Stevenson, Yvonne Helen (Box 249)
  - Stevenson, Yvonne Helen (Box 165)
  - Steward, David E. (Box 166)
  - Steward, Pearl Bank (Box 166)
  - Stewart, John D (Box 166)
  - Strauss, Susan (Box 166)
  - Streano, Vince (Box 166)
  - Stine, Robert (Box 249)
  - Stringer, Arthur J. (Box 166-168)
  - Stobbelaar, John S. (Box 249)
  - Stoffel, Charles R. and Roscoe Burton Starek, III. (Box 249)
  - Stoker, George P. "George Parker" (Box 249)
  - Strauss, Frances (Box 249)
  - Strauss, Sara Mildred (Box 249)
  - Strohnm, Robert (Box 249)
  - Stuart, William L. (Box 250)
  - Stugard, Janet 'Janet Gargisson" (Box 250)
  - Stuller, Jay (Box 250)
  - Sugerman, Andrew and Linda (Box 169)
  - Surguy, Phil (Box 250)
  - Sutherland, Audrey (Box 169)
  - Sutton, Felix (Box 169)
  - Sutton, Felix (Box 250)
  - Swinburne, Algernon Charles (Box 169)
  - Sylvester, Harry (Box 169)
  - Sylvester, Harry (Box 250)
  - T - misc. (Box 250)
  - T - misc. (Box 169)
  - Taber, Scott (Robert Taber) (Box 250)
  - Tarnawsky, Patricia W. "Pat Kilina" (Box 250)
  - Tarnawsky, Patricia W. (Box 169)
  - Tatkon, M. Daniel (Box 169)
  - Taylor, Samuel W. (Box 169)
  - Taylor, Samuel W. (Box 285)
  - Tec, Leon (Box 285)
  - Teitelbaum, William (Box 169)
  - Teller, Judd L. (Box 169)
  - Terrill, Rogers, Literary Agency (Box 169)
  - Terry, Marshall (Box 169)
  - Thapliyal, Sudhir (Box 250)
  - Thomas, James (Box 250)
  - Thurman, Susan R. and Morgan E, Kronk (Box 170)
  - Tobin, Richard L. (Box 250)
  - Toffler, Alvin (Box 170)
  - Toland, John (Box 250)
  - Toland, John (Box 170)
  - Tolstoy, Count Ilya (Box 170)
  - Topor, Tom (Box 170)
  - Torrey, Helen (Box 170)
  - Train, Arthur (Box 170)
  - Tregaskis, Richard (Box 171)
  - Tregaskis, Richard (Box 172)
  - Trevian (Red Whitaker) (Box 250)
  - Trowbridge, Clinton (Box 250)
  - Tuccille, Jerome (Box 172)
  - Tundra Books of Montreal (Box 172)
  - Tung, S.T (Box 172)
  - Tunley, Roul (Box 172)
  - Turnbull, Agnes Sligh (Box 173-175)
  - Turner, John L., III (Box 250)
  - U and V- misc. (Box 250)
  - U - misc. (Box 175)
  - Underhill, Michael (Box 175)
  - V - misc. (Box 175)
  - Valgardson, William D. (Box 251)
  - Valjean, Nelson (Box 175)
  - Van Ash, Cay (Box 175)
  - Vandiver, Frank E. (Box 175)
  - Van Every, Dale (Box 175)
  - Van Fleet, James K. (Box 251)
  - Van Itallie, Philip H. (Box 175)
  - Van Loon, Dirk (Box 176)
  - Van Tuyl, Barbara (Box 176)
  - Verdery, John D. (Box 176)
  - Vicker, Raymond S. (Box 251)
  - Villarreal, Jose Antonio (Box 176)
  - Voronel, Nina (Box 176)
  - W - misc. (Box 176)
  - W- misc. (Box 251)
  - Wahle, H. Anne (Box 177)
  - Wahley, William (Box 251)
  - Wahtera, John (Box 177)
  - Walker, Diana (Box 177)
  - Wallace, Irving (Box 177)
  - Wallace, Irving (Box 251)
  - Wallace, Marcia V. (Box 177)
  - Wallis, Geraldine "Hope Campbell" (Box 177)
  - Walsh, Carol (Carol Gartland) (Box 251)
  - Walt Disney Productions (Box 251)
  - Walter, Richard (Box 251)
  - Walters, Hugh (Box 177)
  - Wanner, Irene (Box 251)
  - Warner, Esther (Esther S.W. Dendel) (Box 177)
  - Warner, Steven (Box 177)
  - Warren, Patricia Nell (Patricia Kilina, Patricia W. Tarnawsky) (Box 177)
  - Wasserman, Richard Edward (Box 177)
  - Waterbury, Ruth (Box 251)
  - Wechsberg, Joseph (Box 252)
  - Wechsberg, Joseph (Box 178-188)
  - Weeks, Morris, Jr. (Box 189)
  - Weidenfeld and Nicolson Limited, George (Box 189)
  - Weisberger, Bernard (Box 189)
  - Weissman, Paul (Box 189)
  - Weglyn, Michi (Box 189)
  - Welsh, Shepherd (Box 189)
  - Wells, Herbert (Box 189)
  - Wertenbaker, Timberlake (Box 252)
  - West, Elliot (Box 189)
  - West, Morris (Box 190-193)
  - West, Morris (Box 252)
  - Whalen, William J. (Box 194)
  - Wheeler, Keith (Box 194)
  - Wheelright, Richard (Box 253)
  - Whitaker, Rod "Trevanian" (Box 194)
  - White, Edgar (Box 253)
  - White, Edward Lucas (Box 194)
  - White, Glenn (Box 253)
  - White, Leslie Turner (Box 194)
  - White, Nancy (Box 253)
  - White, Paul Dudley (Box 195)
  - White, Victoria (Box 253)
  - White, William Lindsay (Box 253)
  - White, William Lindsay (Box 195)
  - White, William Smith and June McConnell (Box 195)
  - White (Box 195)
  - Whitman, Alden (Box 253)
  - Whittaker, Otto (Box 253)
  - Whittemore, L.H. (Box 253)
  - Whittlesey, Eunice S. (Box 195)
  - Wicker, Tom G. (Box 195)
  - Wicker, Tom G. (Box 253)
  - Wicker, Tom G. (Box 196)
  - Wiedenman, Donald (Box 196)
  - Wileoxson, Kent H. (Box 196)
  - Wilde, Oscar (Box 196)
  - Wildes, Harry Emerson (Box 196)
  - Wilhelm, Helen Sanford (Box 197)
  - Willan, Anne (Box 197)
  - Willcox, Sheila (Box 253)
  - Williams, Brad (Box 197)
  - Williams, David (Box 197)
  - Williams, Jeanne Crecy (Box 197)
  - Williams, Lawrence (Box 197)
  - Williams, Ron Maslyn (Box 197)
  - Williamson, Ellen (Box 197)
  - Willis, Roman L. (Box 198)
  - Willis, William (Box 198)
  - Wilson, Eric H. (Box 199)
  - Wilson, Louise A. Stimatorf (Mrs Henry Loel Wilson) (Box 199)
  - Winter, Jack (Box 199)
  - Winter, Stephen (Box 253)
  - Wodehouse, Sir Pelham Grenville 1926-1931 (Box 199A)
  - Wodehouse, Sir Pelham Grenville, 1931-1956 (Box 199B)
  - Wolf, Gary K. (Box 199)
  - Wolfe, H. Leslie (Box 253)
  - Wollaston, Nicholas (Box 199)
  - Wolin, Merle Linda (Box 253)
  - Wolman, Benjamin B. (Box 253)
  - Wolper Pictures, Ltd. (Box 199)
  - Woman's Day (Box 199)
  - Woodley, Richard (Box 253)
  - Worley, Dorothy (Box 253)
  - Worley, Dorothy (Box 199)
  - Wright, Bruce S. (Box 199)
  - Wyatt, Wyatt, Laurence (Box 199)
  - Wyckoff, James (Box 200)
  - Y- misc. (Box 253)
  - Y and Z - misc. (Box 200)
  - Yanker, Gary (Box 200)
  - Yeh, Tsui-pai (Box 200)
  - Yianilos, Theresa Karas and Spero J. Yianilos (Box 200)
  - Youcha, Geraldine (Box 200)
  - Youcha, Geraldine (Box 253)
  - Ypung, Louise B. (Box 200)
  - Yuter, Seymour C. (Box 253)
  - Ziegler Associates, Inc. (Box 200)
  - Zimmerman, Paul D. (Box 200)
  - Misc. unidentified letters (Box 200)
  - Misc. unidentified letters (Box 253)
- Series III: Financial Records
  - Inactive Accounts, 1929-1944 (Box 254)
  - Account Books
    - 1920-1923 (Box 255)
    - 1902-1905 (Box 256)
    - 1905-1915 (Box 257)
    - 1916-1918 (Box 258)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 259)
    - 1917-1924 (Box 260)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 261)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 262)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 263)
    - 1929-1939 (Box 264)
    - 1911-1931 (Box 265)
  - Personal Cash Books
    - 1907-1929 (Box 266)
  - Account Book (Box 267)